isell.com 2014-07-01

# Free Classifieds - Post Free Ads at iSell.com for cars, boats, real estate, jobs and more!

Personally identifiable information you provide iSell.com when you sign up will not be sold or given to outside sources without your permission. iSell.com uses the information we collect in order to provide you with personalized services, such as the Selling and Buying Center, Saved Searches, member ratings/reviews, and account information. 

**Sign-up Information** In order to post, buy, or make an offer for item(s) and service(s) on iSell.com, you must become a iSell.com member. The member registration process requires that you provide your full name, city, state, country and email address. If you were referred to iSell.com from another web site, that web site may send us information that you provided to them. The information they provide is considered private, as if you provided it directly to us. 

**Credit Cards** If you decide to add additional features to your ad such as Featured, Priority Sort, Bold or Highlighting you will be able to enter a credit card for billing convenience through our credit card partner PayPal. In order for the payment process to work properly we must confirm that sign-up information is valid. Members' credit cards will only be charged in accordance with our Fees and Payments Policy. Entering your credit card information on iSell.com is safe; we do not store any credit card information in our system or database and PayPal uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect sensitive data transmissions. 

**Personal Descriptions & Photos** In an effort to facilitate a trusting buying and selling community, we provide you with the option to submit pictures and/or a description of your item or service. When you post your classified ad on iSell.com, the ad description and pictures are displayed on the site and accessible to visitors on iSell.com. We will not allow lewd, nude, or semi-nude photos, so please do not upload them. Classifieds and photos are subject to approval and must meet the Classified Ad Guidelines. 

**Our use of Cookies** iSell.com uses cookies to provide you access to protected pages without requesting a login each time. Cookies are small files that are placed on your computer when you visit our site. Our web site will reference and update the cookie each time you visit iSell.com. We use cookies to deliver content specific to you, for pages such as your Selling and Buying Center. We accomplish this by storing encrypted information that uniquely identifies you in a cookie. 

**Public Access to Information** The information that you provide when you post a classified ad, rate other members, and respond to ratings that others have given you, is posted in public areas and available to all visitors. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, so please exercise caution. 

**Security** This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. All member data and activity is stored separately and is not directly accessible through a web browser. We use industry standard procedures and processes to safeguard the confidentiality of your identifiable personal information, such as firewalls, encryption, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. Unfortunately, when you submit information about yourself to iSell.com over the Internet, the information may travel over many systems that are not under the control of iSell.com. The Internet is not 100% secure and others might intercept the information that you are sending. Remember that your account is accessible only through the use of your Password. 

**Who will have access to my personal information?** Our priority is to keep your personal information private and confidential. iSell.com will not willfully disclose, rent, or sell your personal information to third parties. However, certain personal information will be available to others in the process of using iSell.com. For example, visitors to iSell.com may view your member name, feedback rating, city, and items you have for sale. 

Of course, once you provide personal information to a buyer or seller, iSell.com has no control over how that information might be used by that individual. In addition, should you circumvent our on-site messaging system, iSell.com will be unable to provide assistance in transaction disputes. We recommend using our messaging system for any communications between you and potential buyers and sellers. 

iSell.com may choose to disclose your personally identifiable information to others under the following circumstances: 

  * You consent to share your information. 
  * In response to a criminal investigation, subpoena, court order or legal process. 
  * Your actions on iSell.com appear to be in violation of our policies (including, but not limited to, our Classified Ad Guidelines, User Agreement, and Fees and Payments policies). 
  * You post a classified ad which we believe, in our sole discretion, may create a liability for iSell.com. 

Nothing in this policy shall limit, prohibit, or otherwise deny the ability of iSell.com to (1) transfer, assign, or sell our assets to a third party without limitation, or (2) dispose of our assets in any manner, through bankruptcy or similar proceeding. In addition, iSell.com makes no warranties or claims regarding the accuracy or completeness of the information we collect and disclose through our site, and disclaims any liability regarding its use. 

If needed, you can contact iSell.com or our Security Officer at:

via email: support -at- isell -dot- com  
phone: 1-800-211-7608

iSell.com Worldwide, Inc.  
3120 W. Carefree Hwy  
Suite 1-128  
Phoenix, Arizona 85086
